<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ThingDef ParentName="ResourceBase" Abstract="True" Name="RB_CombBase">
		<storedConceptLearnOpportunity>BenLubarsRimBeesPatches_Combs</storedConceptLearnOpportunity>
		<statBases>
			<MaxHitPoints>10</MaxHitPoints>
			<Flammability>1.0</Flammability>
			<DeteriorationRate>1</DeteriorationRate>
			<Mass>.01</Mass>
			<MarketValue>.1</MarketValue>
		</statBases>
		<tickerType>Normal</tickerType>
		<tradeability>Sellable</tradeability>
		<thingCategories>
			<li>RB_Combs</li>
		</thingCategories>
		<stackLimit>75</stackLimit>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Temperate_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>temperate honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by temperate bees. Temperate bees are the most common type of bee, descended from Earth's Apis Mellifera, the European Honey Bee. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Temperate_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Mild_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>mild honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by mild bees. Mild bees are bees adapted to average temperatures and mild climates, and they produce little honey. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mild_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Hybrid_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>hybrid honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by hybrid bees. Hybrid bees have mixed traits of temperate and mild bees, and are the first step in the creation of specialized bees for the colony. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get white honey and white beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Hybrid_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_WhiteHoney>14</RB_WhiteHoney>
			<RB_WhiteBeeswax>5</RB_WhiteBeeswax>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Amalgam_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>amalgam honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by amalgam bees. Amalgam bees are improved hybrids, and all specialized bees branch from them. They work a bit faster than basic bees. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get blue honey and blue beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Amalgam_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BlueHoney>7</RB_BlueHoney>
			<RB_BlueBeeswax>5</RB_BlueBeeswax>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Alloy_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>alloy honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by alloy bees. Alloy bees are capable of producing honeycombs with metallic compounds in them. Their honey production is minimal, though. The basic Alloy Bee produces steel plated honeycombs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and steel.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Alloy_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Steelwax>10</RB_Steelwax>
			<Steel>5</Steel>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Adaptive_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>adaptive honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by adaptive bees. Adaptive bees are not much affected by the conditions of the biome they are working in. as such, they can stand low and high temperatures a bit better, and they work very fast. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey that doesn't rot and beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Adaptive_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>7</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Neutro_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>neutro honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by neutro bees. Neutro bees capture residual chemical compounds from nearby locations and store them in their honeycombs, producing Neutroamine. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, brittle beeswax and neutroamine.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Neutro_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<Neutroamine>5</Neutroamine>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Nutritious_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>nutritious honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by nutritious bees. Nutritious bees produce fleshy honeycombs that drip blood. This is just disgusting... Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and meat.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Nutritious_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>7</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_NondescriptMeat>25</RB_NondescriptMeat>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Technological_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>technological honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by technological bees. Technological bees are part bee, part machine. They can be further crossbred into bees that provide chemfuel, components, and other technological marvels. But more importantly, they produce Bio Interface Components, which are used to build advanced beehouses. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get heavy beeswax and Bio Interface Components.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Technological_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>20</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_ComponentBioInterface>2</RB_ComponentBioInterface>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Worker_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Worker honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Worker bees, skilled at doing manual work. They don't produce a lot of honey or wax, and no additional comb products, but both them and the bees that are produced by hybridizing them with Amalgam bees can provide extra beehouse effects. In the case of Worker bees, they'll provide a work speed bonus to colonists in the beehouse's area of effect. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Worker_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Commando_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Commando honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Commando bees. Commando bees would NEVER play bee RimWorld without the bee version of Combat Evolved (Combat Evolbeed?). They will viciously attack any hostiles approaching the beehouse's area of effect. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and steelwax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Commando_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Steelwax>3</RB_Steelwax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Research_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Research honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Research bees, adept at investigation and experimentation. On their own, they won't be capable of much (1 point of research per hour), but if you get a considerable number of them they will blow through the colony's research projects in no time. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Research_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Janitor_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Janitor honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Janitor bees. There is nothing Janitor bees despise more than uncleanliness. They will slowly get rid of all filth inside their beehouse's area of effect, as long as it is within the colony's home area. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Janitor_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Stunning_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Stunning honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Stunning bees. Stunning bees absolutely hate mechanoids. They will attack any mechanoids inside their beehouse's area of effect, causing an electric pulse that will stun them in the same manner as EMP grenades. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychothropic honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Eezo_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>3</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Noxious_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Noxious honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Noxious bees. Noxious bees are venomous creatures that... What? Yeah, yeah, I know... all bees are venomous... Ok, these are extra venomous. Venomous deluxe. They will attack any hostiles inside their beehouse's area of effect, causing toxic buildup. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychothropic honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Noxious_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>3</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Tetra_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Tetra honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Tetra bees, pseudo-artificial bees enhanced with the power cores of a Tetra slug. They are capable of slowly recharging nearby batteries. It is probably not a good idea to use a beehouse that consumes power for these, as the effect would cancel out... These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Tetra_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Skilful_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Skilful honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Skilful bees. Natural born tinkerers, they are capable of repairing structures and keeping them in working order. They will slowly repair buildings inside their beehouse's area of effect. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and steelwax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Prefab_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Steelwax>3</RB_Steelwax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Blazing_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Blazing honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Blazing bees. While blazing bees don't have the astounding temperature range of desert bees, their bodies irradiate enormous amounts of heat. They will increase the temperature around their beehouse until it reaches 30 degrees, as long as it is indoors. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and red beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Blazing_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_RedBeeswax>3</RB_RedBeeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Frigid_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Frigid honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Frigid bees. While Frigid bees don't have the astounding temperature range of arctic bees, their bodies absorb enormous amounts of heat from the air. They will reduce the temperature around their beehouse until it reaches -10 degrees, as long as it is indoors. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Frigid_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>3</RB_Beeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Foamy_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Foamy honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Foamy bees. Foamy bees despise fire. They gather certain chemicals from their environment and transform them into a potent mixture that is capable of extinguishing nearby fires. These honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey and red beeswax, though at very small amounts.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Foamy_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>3</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_RedBeeswax>3</RB_RedBeeswax>
			
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Arctic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>arctic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by arctic bees. Arctic bees have adapted to the colder climates on the Rim, and their honeycombs store honey and frost in equal amounts. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, beeswax and ice pops.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Arctic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>10</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<RB_HoneyedIcePop>15</RB_HoneyedIcePop>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Woodland_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>woodland honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by woodland bees. Woodland bees feel happily at home surrounded by lots of trees. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, beeswax and wood logs.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Woodland_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>10</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<WoodLog>10</WoodLog>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Desert_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>desert honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by desert bees. Its wax has a parched texture, partly built with the surrounding sand. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, red beeswax and agave.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Desert_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_RedBeeswax>10</RB_RedBeeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<RawAgave>25</RawAgave>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Swamp_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>swamp honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by swamp bees. A gelatinous substance covers the whole comb, seemingly to protect its contents from the high humidity of the environment. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, beeswax and mushrooms.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Swamp_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<RawFungus>25</RawFungus>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Nocturnal_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>nocturnal honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by nocturnal bees. It is pitch black, and radiates cold. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get black honey and black beeswax.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Nocturnal_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BlackBeeswax>10</RB_BlackBeeswax>
			<RB_BlackHoney>5</RB_BlackHoney>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Argent_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>argent honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by argent bees. It's surface is very sparkly, you could almost use it as a mirror! Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and silver.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Argent_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Steelwax>10</RB_Steelwax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<Silver>25</Silver>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Aurum_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>aurum honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by aurum bees. It's golden surface could probably fetch a decent price in any market, but it is much better to extract the gold from it. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and gold.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Aurum_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Steelwax>5</RB_Steelwax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<Gold>10</Gold>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Precious_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>precious honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by precious bees. Sparkly! Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and jade.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Precious_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Steelwax>5</RB_Steelwax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<Jade>10</Jade>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Radioactive_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>radioactive honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by radioactive bees. All things considered, your colonists are lucky that programming a radioactivity system is well beyond the scope of this mod. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and uranium.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Radioactive_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Steelwax>5</RB_Steelwax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<Uranium>10</Uranium>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Tipsy_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>tipsy honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by tipsy bees. It is saturated with wort, which can then be fermented into beer. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, brittle beeswax and wort.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Tipsy_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<Wort>5</Wort>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Luxurious_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>luxurious honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by luxurious bees, which are able to concentrate pollen in an amazing way, turning it into ambrosia, a very mild drug that is widely used on the Rim. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, brittle beeswax and ambrosia.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Luxurious_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>10</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<Ambrosia>5</Ambrosia>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Psychic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>psychic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Psychic bees, who know everything and see everything. Not because they are wise ancient seers, but because their tiny bodies are saturated with psychite compounds. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, brittle beeswax and psychoid leaves.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Psychic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<PsychoidLeaves>25</PsychoidLeaves>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Stoner_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>stoner honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Stoner bees, and smells like certain hotels in Amsterdam. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, brittle beeswax and smokeleaf leaves.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Stoner_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<SmokeleafLeaves>25</SmokeleafLeaves>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Agricultural_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>agricultural honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Agricultural bees, which are hard workers, extracting grain from their environment and stuffing their honeycombs full of strange undiferentiated seeds. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and vegetables.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Agricultural_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>1</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_NonDescriptVegetables>35</RB_NonDescriptVegetables>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Bittersweet_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>bittersweet honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Bittersweet bees, who LOVE chocolate and try to fill their combs with it. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and chocolate.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Bittersweet_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>1</RB_TastyHoney>
			<Chocolate>10</Chocolate>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Lactic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>lactic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Lactic bees. It is filled with a strange liquid that can be considered milk, if you ignore its origins... Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and milk.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Lactic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>2</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_BeeMilk>10</RB_BeeMilk>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Egglaying_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>egglaying honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Egglaying bees. It is filled with a lot of really small spheres that can be considered regular eggs, if you ignore their origins... Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and eggs.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Egglaying_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>2</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_BeeEggs>5</RB_BeeEggs>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Insectoid_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>insectoid honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Insectoid bees. Insectoid bees are part insect... Wait... But all bees are... Nevermind, these bees produce insect jelly just like the insectoids that insist on being a nuisance to your colony. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, heavy beeswax and insect jelly.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Insectoid_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>5</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>3</RB_TastyHoney>
			<InsectJelly>10</InsectJelly>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Electronic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>electronic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Electronic bees. It doesn't even seem to be organic! Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and industrial components.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Electronic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>5</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<ComponentIndustrial>1</ComponentIndustrial>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Oily_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>oily honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Oily bees. It is completely drenched in a chemical solution, and it can be easily extracted and turned into Chemfuel. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and chemfuel.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Oily_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>10</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<Chemfuel>12</Chemfuel>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Plastic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>plastic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Plastic bees. It seems to be reinforced with a natural plasteel lattice. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and plasteel.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Plastic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>15</RB_HeavyWax>
			<Plasteel>5</Plasteel>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Quarry_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>quarry honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by quarry bees, which can extract small amounts of stone from the landscape and turn them into granite chunks. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and granite chunks.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Quarry_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>15</RB_HeavyWax>
			<ChunkGranite>1</ChunkGranite>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Mason_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>mason honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by mason bees, which are adept at taking stone from the landscape and sculpting it into granite blocks. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and granite blocks.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mason_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>15</RB_HeavyWax>
			<BlocksGranite>25</BlocksGranite>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Pet_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>pet honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Pet bees. Pet bees really care about all other animals, and they'd like you to have a LOT of pets running around the colony. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and kibble.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Pet_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>10</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<Kibble>25</Kibble>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Rainbow_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>rainbow honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by rainbow bees, who love decoration and gaudy colours. They can collect multicoloured honey and saturate their combs with dye. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and dye.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Rainbow_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>10</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<Dye>5</Dye>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Straw_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>straw honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by straw bees. Straw bees slowly collect loose dry grass lying around and weave it into their honeycombs. These strands can then be extracted from the comb and turned into useable Hay. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, brittle beeswax and hay.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Straw_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>10</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>7</RB_Brittlewax>
			<Hay>25</Hay>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Weaving_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>weaving honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Weaving bees. Weaving bees are all about knitting, crocheting and felting. It's all they care to do in their spare time. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, brittle beeswax and cloth.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Weaving_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<Cloth>25</Cloth>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Tanner_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>tanner honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Tanner bees. Tanner bees are capable of creating a pseudo-artificial leather without needing to kill any animals. Vegans will be super pleased! Well, except for the whole enslaving entire colonies of bees, that is... Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, heavy beeswax and leather.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Tanner_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>5</RB_HeavyWax>
			<Leather_Plain>25</Leather_Plain>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Wooly_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>wooly honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Wooly bees. Wooly bees are miniature insects covered in a dense fur. Which is not the source of any nightmares at all, no sir! Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and wool.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Wooly_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>10</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<WoolMuffalo>10</WoolMuffalo>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_High_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>high honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by High bees. High bees are junkies, permanently high on yayo. This makes them pretty terrible workers, but they produce a significant, constant amount of drugs, which accumulates on their combs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, beeswax and yayo.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_High_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>10</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<Yayo>5</Yayo>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Lucifer_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>lucifer honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Lucifer bees. An entire breed of bees addicted to luciferium. Lucifer bees are the slowest working bees possible, what with the constant dying and suffering but they produce a significant, constant amount of luciferium, which accumulates on their combs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get psychotropic honey, red beeswax and luciferium.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Lucifer_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_RedBeeswax>5</RB_RedBeeswax>
			<Luciferium>1</Luciferium>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Culinary_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>culinary honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Culinary bees. Culinary bees like to cook. They are not very good at it, but the poor critters try to do their best. Their combs have a nutrient paste that can be processed into a very simple meal. Not appetizing, but edible. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and nutrient paste.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Culinary_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>30</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<MealNutrientPaste>1</MealNutrientPaste>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Chef_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>chef honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Chef bees. Chef bees REALLY do like to cook! And they are surprisingly good at it, too! They accumulate different ingredients on their combs, and those can be easily turned into a meal of decent quality. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and fine meals.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Chef_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>35</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>15</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_FineHoney>1</RB_FineHoney>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Medicinal_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>medicinal honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Medicinal bees. Medicinal bees secrete a saline solution that can be used as a low grade medicinal salve. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and herbal medicine.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Medicinal_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>10</RB_Beeswax>
			<MedicineHerbal>1</MedicineHerbal>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Surgeon_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>surgeon honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Surgeon bees. Surgeon bees secrete a more powerful version of the saline solution produced by medicinal bees, but they also had to study more years at University. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and medicine.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Surgeon_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>15</RB_Beeswax>
			<MedicineIndustrial>1</MedicineIndustrial>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Glittering_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>Glittering honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Glittering bees. They secrete a healing solution infused with nanites, saturating their combs with an immensely powerful medicine. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and glitterworld medicine.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Glittering_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>10</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>15</RB_Beeswax>
			<MedicineUltratech>1</MedicineUltratech>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Synthetic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>synthetic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Synthetic bees. Synthetic bees catch minute fibres from the air surrounding them and weave them with a natural silk to create synthread, which they spun in their combs, ready to be harvested. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and synthread.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Synthetic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>1</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>25</RB_Beeswax>
			<Synthread>5</Synthread>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Hyper_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>hyper honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Hyper bees. SHyper bees catch minute fibres from the air surrounding them and weave them with a natural silk to create hyperthread, which they spun in their combs, ready to be harvested. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and hyperweave.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Hyper_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>1</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>30</RB_Beeswax>
			<Hyperweave>5</Hyperweave>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Nitro_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>nitro honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Nitro bees. These bees synthesize a very unstable compound that can be extracted to create explosive mortar shells. They work very slow, though, and they'll need a stockpile with a little bit of Chemfuel nearby to start refining its compounds. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get white honey, heavy beeswax and explosive mortar shells.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Nitro_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>10</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_WhiteHoney>7</RB_WhiteHoney>
			<Shell_HighExplosive>1</Shell_HighExplosive>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Fabricated_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>fabricated honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Fabricated bees. Fabricated bees synthesize technology and refine it into a more advanced form. They'll need a stockpile with Components nearby and they'll slowly incorporate them into their honeycombs as Advanced Components. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get white honey, heavy beeswax and advanced components.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Fabricated_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_HeavyWax>15</RB_HeavyWax>
			<RB_WhiteHoney>15</RB_WhiteHoney>
			<ComponentSpacer>1</ComponentSpacer>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
</Defs>
