<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Mutagenic_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>mutagenic honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by mutagenic bees. They are in constant flux, with random animal parts mutating and merging through their whole body. As long as a vial of mutagenic Mechanite Slurry is nearby, these bees will collect it and store it in their honeycombs, slowly producing more of it. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get Psychotropic honey, brittlewax and Mechanite Slurry.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mutagenic_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>	
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<MechaniteSlurry>1</MechaniteSlurry>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Mutanite_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>mutanite honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by mutanite bees, which are infused with the sickening green glow of dangerous activated mechanites. If a chunk of mutanite is placed nearby, the bees will gradually though very slowly replicate more of it on their honeycombs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get Psychotropic honey, heavywax and mutanite chunks.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mutanite_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>	
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>15</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>15</RB_HeavyWax>
			<Mutanite>1</Mutanite>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Morph_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>morph honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by morph bees, which are expert weavers, intricately lacing cloth with mutagenic nanites. As long as a piece of Morphsilk is nearby, they will replicate the pattern and slowly weave it into their combs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get Psychotropic honey, brittlewax and Morphsilk.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mutanite_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>	
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_PsychotropicHoney>5</RB_PsychotropicHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>7</RB_Brittlewax>
			<Morphsilk>2</Morphsilk>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>


</Defs>
