<ModMetaData>
	<name>RimBees</name>
	<author>Sarg</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.0</li></supportedVersions>
	<description>Breed bees to generate all kinds of resources!

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;

- Beekeeping: find wild bees in all biomes, build beehouses to put them to work! A single beehouse won't do much, so prepare to build a few. Are you in an extreme biome? There are low-efficiency climatized beehouses available for you until you can get bees that modify allowed temperatures!
- Bee breeding: Mix two breeds of bees in a beehouse, and use a brood chamber to multiply them, and an hybridization chamber to get new species (more than 30)!
- Honey making: Centrifuge the combs produced by the bees to get honey and wax.
- Cooking and building: honey can be used as an ingredient in cooking, and wax can be used as a building material.
- Mead brewing: turn honey into mead to make your colonists happy (and drunk)
- Wax lighting: candles are a quaint and cheap way to light your base
- Resource gathering: many of the bees produce combs with more things than honey and wax. Will you find the Luciferium-producing bees?

&lt;size=24&gt;Issues&lt;/size&gt;

This mod is more complex than other mods I have worked on previously (Genetic Rim and Alpha Animals), so expect some weird issues from time to time. Please report them with an error log if possible.
Also, balance. Balance is always a work in progress!

&lt;size=24&gt;Plans for the future&lt;/size&gt;

More bees!

&lt;size=24&gt;Credit&lt;/size&gt;

Building texture modified from Textures by Pixel Art World, http://yms.main.jp
Fancy Food Items by KanaX: https://forums.rpgmakerweb.com/index.php?threads/fancy-food-items.44398/
Honeyed Ice Pop by Game Developer Studio (Robert Brooks): https://opengameart.org/content/ice-pops
Wax floor textures from the Apini Mod: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=31076.0

&lt;size=24&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;

Right now, the mod shouldn't give problems. In the future, I'll add patches to make new bee species that give modded materials

&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;

v1.02: Bugfixes (06/03/19)
v1.01: Bugfixes. Added rotatable workbenches (12/11/18)
v1.0: Release version (06/11/18)


		</description>
</ModMetaData>
