<ModMetaData>
	<name>RimBees</name>
	<author>Sarg</author>
	<supportedVersions>
      <li>1.0</li>
      <li>1.1</li>
	  <li>1.2</li>
   </supportedVersions>
   <modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<packageId>sarg.rimbees</packageId>
	<description>Breed bees to generate all kinds of resources! 

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;

- Beekeeping: find wild bees in all biomes, build beehouses to put them to work! A single beehouse won't do much, so prepare to build a few. Are you in an extreme biome? There are low-efficiency climatized beehouses available for you until you can get bees that modify allowed temperatures! 
- Bee breeding: Mix two breeds of bees in a beehouse, and use a brood chamber to multiply them, and an hybridization chamber to get new species (more than 30)!
- Honey making: Centrifuge the combs produced by the bees to get honey and wax
- Cooking and building: honey can be used as an ingredient in cooking, and wax can be used as a building material
- Mead brewing: turn honey into mead to make your colonists happy (and drunk)
- Wax lighting: candles are a quaint and cheap way to light your base
- Resource gathering: many of the bees produce combs with more things than honey and wax. Will you find the Luciferium-producing bees?
- Research: discover new exciting bee combinations
- Pollination: plan your growing zones around your beehives and increase your crop production

&lt;size=24&gt;Issues&lt;/size&gt;

Balance is always a work in progress!

&lt;size=24&gt;Plans for the future&lt;/size&gt;

More bees!

&lt;size=24&gt;Credit&lt;/size&gt;

Fancy Food Items by KanaX: https://forums.rpgmakerweb.com/index.php?threads/fancy-food-items.44398/
Wax floor textures from the Apini Mod: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=31076.0
Thanks to TheSevenSins for helping on the 2.0 update

&lt;size=24&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;

Right now, the mod shouldn't give problems. In the future, I'll add patches to make new bee species that give modded materials

&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;

v4.1: Updated for RimWorld 1.2 (11/08/20)
v4.0: Complete retexture of the mod from the gound up (30/07/20)
v3.0: Updated for RimWorld 1.1 (09/03/20)
v2.07: Beehouses' bee lists are now ordered alphabetically (15/12/19)
v2.06: Added LWM's Deep Storage, the Bee Rack (30/11/19)
v2.05: Added option to remove hybridization messages. Added bee result info to hybridization messages (29/11/19)
v2.04: Added mod options, including greenhouse bees, ignoring rain, night-time, etc. Adjusted bee insertion timeout to be three times previous (16/11/19)
v2.032: Added mushroom tree hives for the Mycotic Forest in Alpha Biomes (10/11/19)
v2.031: Fixed bug with mead fermenting barrels (4/11/19)
v2.03: Fixed bug with pollination were multiple plants were appearing. Increased temp range of wild beehives. Added metallic stuffing to beehouses and climatized beehouses (06/10/19)
v2.02: Fixed bug were advanced climatized beehouses were not working properly (30/09/19)
v2.01: Added properties to honeys so they transfer their special stats to meads and other food. Fixed adding chambers to beehouse blueprints. Added an option to automatically add a growing zone around beehouses (29/09/19)
v2.0: Updated everything. Beekeeping work type, queueing of bee jobs, externalization of most code on XML files, "extract from any comb" recipe, added 8 new bees, new combs, new honeys, new waxes. Seriously, check the changelog on GitHub because I almost rewrote the entire mod (26/09/19)
v1.02: Bugfixes (06/03/19)
v1.01: Bugfixes. Added rotatable workbenches (12/11/18)
v1.0: Release version (06/11/18)


		</description>
</ModMetaData>
