<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<!-- Combs -->
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Aero_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>aero honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by aero bees, which are translucent bees filled with blue-tinted hydrogen gas. They collect blue gel in their honeycombs. Honeycombs can be processed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, brittle beeswax, and blue gel.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Aero_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>5</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>								
			<AA_BlueGel>5</AA_BlueGel>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Black_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>black honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by black bees. They are tiny genetically engineered insectoids created to destroy mechanoids. Unfortunately they are so small that they can't do much, but they store small amounts of black chitin and black hive insect jelly on their honeycombs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax, black chitin and black hive insect jelly.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Black_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<Leather_BlackChitin>5</Leather_BlackChitin>
			<AA_BlackInsectJelly>5</AA_BlackInsectJelly>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Cactus_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>cactus honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by cactus bees, which are part animal, part plant. Their honeycombs are semi-edible, producing a weird cactus meat that counts as a vegetable, and medicinal cactipine quills. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, brittle beeswax, cactus meat and medicinal cactipine quills.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Cactus_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>5</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<AA_CactusMeat>10</AA_CactusMeat>
			<AA_CactipineQuill>1</AA_CactipineQuill>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Devil_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>devil honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by devil bees, which have a piercing gaze that seems to look into your soul. They are expert devilstrand producers, cultivating the strange fungus inside their beehouses. They will need a small amount of devilstrand planted nearby to gather spores. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and devilstrand.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Devil_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>15</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>15</RB_Beeswax>
			<DevilstrandCloth>15</DevilstrandCloth>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Feral_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>feral honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by feral bees. They share some of the best -and worst- characteristics of the Cinderlisk spiders. Their tiny mandibles are always burning-hot, and they can slowly gather cotton fibers from nearby plants and convert them into Cindersilk. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and Cindersilk.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Feral_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>15</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Beeswax>15</RB_Beeswax>
			<AA_CinderSilk>15</AA_CinderSilk>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Forsaken_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>forsaken honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Forsaken bees. They originate from a RimWorld orbiting a very faint star -the native planet of an elusive alien spacies know as Forsakens- so they have adapted to environments with low sunlight. They produce small amounts of Night Leather. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get black honey, black beeswax and night leather.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Forsaken_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BlackBeeswax>10</RB_BlackBeeswax>
			<RB_BlackHoney>5</RB_BlackHoney>
			<Leather_Night>5</Leather_Night>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Frosty_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>frosty honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Frosty bees, creatures adapted to extreme low temperatures, feeding on half inorganic vegetation present in the unnatural propane lakes. Frosty bees regularly produce Blue Milk. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, beeswax and blue milk.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Frosty_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_TastyHoney>2</RB_TastyHoney>
			<AA_BlueMilk>10</AA_BlueMilk>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Fungal_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>fungal honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Fungal bees, sentient mycoid creatures adapted to life in jungle infested planets on the Rim. Their whole body is covered in apparently decomposing plant matter. They grow Raw Agarilux mushrooms inside their honeycombs. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, beeswax and raw agarilux mushrooms.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Fungal_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Beeswax>5</RB_Beeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>6</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<AA_AgariluxRawFungus>30</AA_AgariluxRawFungus>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Legendary_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>legendary honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Legendary bees. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get tasty honey, heavy beeswax and Gallatross leather.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Legendary_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_TastyHoney>20</RB_TastyHoney>
			<RB_HeavyWax>30</RB_HeavyWax>
			<Leather_Gallatross>25</Leather_Gallatross>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Ocular_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>ocular honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Ocular bees, unnerving trans-dimensional beings that slowly convert and twist nearby vegetation into completely alien flora. They slowly accumulate Red Wood in their honeycombs. Besides producing honeycombs that provide red wood logs, these bees will also cut down trees that are designated by the player inside their beehouse's radius of effect. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, red beeswax and red wood logs.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Ocular_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_RedBeeswax>10</RB_RedBeeswax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<GU_RedWood>10</GU_RedWood>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Slimy_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>slimy honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Slimy bees, amorphous, ambulatory masses of gelatinous fluid in the approximate shape of a bee. In reality they are part of a greater gelatinous superorganism, with only one objective: grow and expand. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get adaptive honey, brittle beeswax and obscene amounts of raw red slime.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Slimy_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_Brittlewax>5</RB_Brittlewax>
			<RB_AdaptiveHoney>5</RB_AdaptiveHoney>
			<AB_RawRedSlime>125</AB_RawRedSlime>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Slurry_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>slurry honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Slurry bees. They are tiny mechanoid bees that consume practically anything in the vicinity and transform it into obscene amounts of a refined paste meal that is unbelievably disgusting for sapient beings, and sometimes an industrial component. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get a lot of disgusting nutrient paste meals and industrial components.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Slurry_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<AA_DisgustingMealNutrientPaste>20</AA_DisgustingMealNutrientPaste>
			<ComponentIndustrial>1</ComponentIndustrial>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>
	<ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Sky_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>sky honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by Sky bees, serpentine bees adept at converting Steel into a stronger version of it, Sky Steel. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, steelwax and sky steel.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Sky_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_BaseHoney>5</RB_BaseHoney>
			<RB_Steelwax>12</RB_Steelwax>
			<AA_SkySteel>8</AA_SkySteel>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef>




</Defs>
